Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series Men in Lace
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series Men in lace
1988-1996
Bailey 4
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
88 v.; 17-18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
Some individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All individual titles paperbound.
Some individual titles also have series-like title: A crossdressing romance ...
Some series numbers repeat; these titles called 2nd series.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- Men In Lace
  - Virgin swinger, c1988; ML_101_ (Box 101-134)
  - Two into one, c1988; ML_102_ (Box 101-134)
  - Their stud gardener, c1988; ML_103_ (Box 101-134)
  - Bisexual beauty queen, c1988 (first printing 1982); ML_104_ (Box 101-134)
  - Lingerie lovers, c1988; ML_105_ (Box 101-134)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on top edge: MBI
  - Forced into satin, c1988; ML_106_ (Box 101-134)
  - Her man maiden, c1988; ML_107_ (Box 101-134)
  - Dressed for sex, c1988 (first printing 1980); ML_108_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: 47
  - Satin jock, c1989; ML_109_ (Box 101-134)
  - Laced to serve, c1989; ML_110_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: CBD
  - Frilly stud, c1989; ML_111_ (Box 101-134)
  - Forced to be she-male, c1989 (first printing 1980); ML_112_ (Box 101-134)
  - Tight corset, c1989; ML_113_ (Box 101-134)
  - Training bra jock, c1989; ML_114_ (Box 101-134)
  - Whipped into panties, c1989; ML_115_ (Box 101-134)
  - Tough women/feminized men, c1989 (first printing 1980); ML_116_ (Box 101-134)
  - Maid to obey, c1989; ML_117_ (Box 101-134)
  - The corset shop, c1989; ML_118_ (Box 101-134)
  - Husband in training, c1989; ML_119_ (Box 101-134)
  - Cross-dressed banker, c1989 (first printing 1980); ML_120_ (Box 101-134)
  - Torrid man tamer, c1989; ML_121_ (Box 101-134)
  - Frills on Bill's, c1989; ML_122_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: #46
  - Crossdressed to serve, c1989; ML_123_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: MapMapMap
  - Madame's TV slave, c1989 (first printing 1980); ML_124_ (Box 101-134)
  - Trained to be female, c1989; ML_125_ (Box 101-134)
  - Boy-girl slave, c1989; ML_126_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on top edge: 0401023560
  - The training, c1989; ML_127_ (Box 101-134)
    Price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.
  - Shamed schoolboy, c1989 (first printing 1983); ML_128_ (Box 101-134)
  - Fixed on frills, c1990; ML_129_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: CBD. Price label on back cover, partially obscuring text.
  - Pampered she-male, c1990; ML_130_ (Box 101-134)
  - Max in make-up, c1990; ML_131_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: MapMapMap
  - Twin delights, c1990 (first printing 1983); ML_132_ (Box 101-134)
  - Dalton, c1990; ML_133_ (Box 101-134)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - TV's first date, c1990; ML_134_ (Box 101-134)
  - Maid of the man, c1990; ML_135_ (Box 135-204)
  - Jock in lace, c1990 (first printing 1985); ML_136_ (Box 135-204)
    Price label on front cover. Inventory label (?) on back cover, partially obscuring text: 36.
  - The babysitter, c1990; ML_137_ (Box 135-204)
  - Bob, c1990; ML_138_ (Box 135-204)
  - Lane, c1990; ML_139_ (Box 135-204)
  - Black booted bitch, c1990 (first printing 1980); ML_140_ (Box 135-204)
  - Nikki, c1991; ML_141_ (Box 135-204)
  - Sam, c1991; ML_142_ (Box 135-204)
  - Karen, c1991; ML_143_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on bottom edge: SODI [?]
  - TV hostage, c1991 (first printing 1988); ML_144_ (Box 135-204)
  - The broker wore lace, c1991; ML_145_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on bottom edge: 39
  - Lies and lace, c1991; ML_146_ (Box 135-204)
  - Millie/Willie, c1991; ML_147_ (Box 135-204)
  - Husband in training, c1991 (first printing 1989); ML_148_ (Box 135-204)
    Inventory label (?) on front cover: 11/01/91 +4178.94
  - Tracy, c1992; ML_149_ (Box 135-204)
  - Doc dress-up, c1992; ML_150_ (Box 135-204)
  - The corset shop, c1992 (first printing 1989); ML_151_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on top edge: 35
  - Virgin swinger, c1992 (first printing 1988); ML_152_ (Box 135-204)
  - Crossdressed pro, c1992; ML_153_ (Box 135-204)
  - Pretty boy, c1992; ML_154_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on top edge: 15
  - He wore a bra, c1992 (first printing 1989); ML_155_ (Box 135-204)
  - Satin stud, c1992 (first printing 1989); ML_156_ (Box 135-204)
  - Bobby's frills, c1993 (first printing 1987, under title "Bobby in frills"); ML_157_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist. Stamp on bottom edge: SODI
  - The maid's a man, c1993 (first printing 1989); ML_158_ (Box 135-204)
    Stamp on top edge: Map [?]. Price label on back cover, partially obscuring text.
  - His panty fetish, c1993 (first printing 1990, under title "Dalton"); ML_159_ (Box 135-204)
  - His first date, c1993 (first printing 1990, under title "TV's first date"); ML_160_ (Box 135-204)
  - Dressed to please, c1993; ML_161_ (Box 135-204)
  - Maid of the man, c1993 (first printing 1990); ML_162_ (Box 135-204)
  - Crossdressed submissive, c1993 (first printing 1981); ML_163_ (Box 135-204)
  - Jock in lace, c1993 (first printing 1985, reprinted 1990); ML_164_ (Box 135-204)
  - Bound in lace, c1996; ML_166_ (Box 135-204)
  - The babysitter, c1997; ML_201_ (Box 135-204)
  - Their stud gardener, c1997; ML_202_ (Box 135-204)
    "Copy 1: Inventory label (?) on front cover, partially obscuring text: Stud. Gard. 202 rtn.by.9/02/97 Copy 2: Barcode/price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill."
  - Bitch in black boots, c1997; ML_203_ (Box 135-204)
    Barcode/price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.
  - Dressed for sex, c1997; ML_204_ (Box 135-204)
  - The pimp wore dresses, c1994 (first printing 1986); ML_133 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Satin nights, c1994 (first printing 1986); ML_134 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Billy's frillies, c1994 (first printing 1987); ML_135 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Banker's secret lust, c1994; ML_136 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Crossdressed pro, c1995; ML_137 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Geoffrey's secret, c1995; ML_138 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Stamp on top edge: CVD
  - He wore a bra, c1995 (first printing 1989); ML_139 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Price label on front cover: DAB Inc., 634-4705, 16
  - Satin stud, c1995 (first printing 1989); ML_140 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    "Price label on front cover: 17 AEN $4.95 Barcode label on back cover"
  - Tim or Tina?, c1995; ML_141 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist [?]
  - Brother bombschell, c1995; ML_142 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist
  - Nine inches in a nighte [sic], c1995; ML_143 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist
  - Hardbody toy, c1995; ML_144 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Sebastian's stockings, c1996; ML_166 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    "Stamp on top edge: 03 Price label on front cover: $5.95+tx"
  - Darcy's hard surprise, c1996; ML_167 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
  - Pretty young guy, c1996; ML_168 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Undeciphered stamp on top edge
  - One guy's garter-belt, c1996; ML_169 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Stamp on top edge: MAP MAP MAP
  - Sissy stud, c1996; ML_170 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    "Stamp on top edge: MAP MAP MAP Barcode label on back cover"
  - Brute in a negligee, c1996; ML_171 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Barcode & price label on front cover: Rtn. by 8/14/96 $5.95
  - She-male homebody, c1996; ML_172 [2nd series]_ (Box II:133-II:172)
    Inventory (?) label on front cover: 7/25/96 427[3]852